what's up y'all welcome to the junkyard
love podcast
i'm happy you're here if you're joining
me on youtube
and you're watching this video welcome
to the weirdest camera angle ever
i just wanted to get this intro in there
and done and ready to go
plugged into the episode so you guys can
get listening to me and megan robinson
it's a good combo
um what what you missed the first couple
minutes i actually
hit record on zoom a little late so
you're coming into a conversation five
minutes after we had started it
what you missed in the beginning was
basically me explaining that i had just
broken a 46 hour fast i was doing a
uh uh an extended fast to mourn the loss
of a
um a family member and friend of mine so
i was a little
a bit loopy kind of maybe a little um
scattered it's
uh it it helps with some cognitive
areas but it kind of enhances adhd to
some extent
so um i was a little bit all over the
place but that was kind of explaining
that at the beginning of the episode and
then megan and i began talking about
um you know diet and fasting and these
sorts of things and that's
that's where you guys tune in so that's
the episode
um it's pretty good if you guys are
enjoying this please
subscribe like share all that sort of
thing
if you want to check out clips or
trailers i'm going to have a
youtube channel going shortly junkyard
love podcast clips
that can be found on the junkyard love
just search junkyardlove on youtube and
you should be able to find it
and then if if you'd like to also watch
some clips uh
that i post to social media i'm not
interacting with on social media right
now but i am posting i'm posting and
ghosting only
so um check out my
social media page on instagram jacob
from the internet
all one word and shortly youtube will
all be changing to jacob from the
internet
and the junkyard love podcast will just
be under the jacob from the internet
channel
and then i think i'll still do a
separate junkyard love podcast clip so
that's where we're at with all that i
really appreciate you guys listening i
really appreciate any
interaction if you do like this episode
if you do like anything that's said in
here if you like a clip or whatever it
is
you know share it with your friends
leave a comment the interaction
does help um this is it's all really
just just word of mouth
how i'm advertising this i don't really
pay for any promotion or anything like
that so
what you guys share is is how people
listen i appreciate it
take care of yourselves stretch wherever
you're at get present
use your five senses enjoy the episode
we'll see you next week hello and
welcome to the junkyard love
podcast
at what age do we learn how to have
better conversations
at what age do we learn to have better
conversations with ourselves
[Music]
knowledge is power
reality
[Music]
it's is very good i think i've lost like
40 pounds off of doing that
so oh that's good yeah congrats on that
isn't that interesting how how we feel
like just because there is you know the
extreme levels of eating disorders
or you know bulimia or anorexia or
you know like people who have really bad
binge eating habits or whatever it is
we we somehow a lot of us feel like oh i
don't want to identify like i'm not
trying to take away anything from you
but i do have my own versions of it
because i have my you know
looking at me and someone might roll
their eyes but i i have problems with
binge eating like it's an emotional
thing
um and so but you know i i think
learning how your body works and trying
to just you know
because so so you learned that counting
all your calories and being like
you know super strict about it doesn't
exactly work like being overly strict
about it kind of crushes it
right yeah no and for me like i knew
that wanting to monitor
how much i ate and like my intake and
outtake was sort of like a gateway to
like a larger trigger
of how i was when i was in high school
and i would just like just not eat it
wasn't like intermediate fast and i just
went eat
and then like when i would eat it was
like such a little amount of calories
and then i'd want to like work off those
galleries
but and then like i passed out a few
times and that was sort of like a red
alert of like okay i shouldn't do this
anymore this is really bad
and then i sort of like during college
like swung the opposite way where it was
like all right well i'm stressed
there's all this free food everywhere
because college i'm gonna eat all of it
and then
that also wasn't the right way to do it
either but
like so many people have and i mean i
guess it's
it's wrong i'm sure there's some sort of
psychological title for it but
because i know of people that have had
it worse or have had to like go to rehab
for
or have um you know been in the hospital
for long periods of time or
you know have turned into nothing i
don't want to
put myself in that same like label as
like anybody
else that had it that bad but like i
know
that that is like a trigger for me that
like that's not something that i should
do
because i then i'll get like maybe
addicted to that idea again and then
like fall back into that path isn't that
so crazy man like just getting older
we're realizing how
i mean food and diet in our nutrition
turns out to be one of the most
confusing things to handle
like we i mean growing up that we were
always trying to like
okay well you know i want to look this
way or i want to you know
i want to um eat these foods so i can
fit into this or
or whatever it is but then as i've
gotten older i'm like how do i feel
how do i feel you know like if my
mental's not feeling good if i'm feeling
tired if i'm feeling
off like i just i really want my body to
feel good
and then if if it looks good you know
that's a cool side effect but it's it's
an exploration as we get older and as
we're learning more about food and
you know all this nutrition stuff about
the microbiome and
all these you know we think that it's
just calories and
and um you know bad calories
make you fat but there's also these
there's like
uh these bad oils that are good not good
for your stomach
there's all these little extra you know
gmos we still don't really know if
they're gonna give us
third arms growing out of our back or
what's gonna happen there
so it's nutrition is super complicated
honestly
no and like it's nutrition and like what
you're like we're an engine so like
whatever we give our body that we're
used to
so like i'm kind of addicted to coffee
but like you know i know that if i wake
up
i'm used to having a cup of coffee so
like you know when i'm traveling and
stuff and there's not always like a
starbucks goes by and i don't have that
coffee midday i'm going to feel kind of
poopy
and just because my engine is expecting
like okay you're going to give me a
burst of caffeine
right like i'm not used to giving it to
you that and like even recently i've
been
like the way the world is right now i've
been super into like my vitamins and
like
um but you know all the little packs i
drink like a
vitamin c like energy see every day and
so on a day where like i skipped that
the next day i feel it and it's like oh
why
i was like oh i didn't i didn't take
this yesterday and
like my engine just doesn't feel as good
yeah you gotta you gotta keep your
engine tuned up isn't it isn't it crazy
you can notice those very it's very
subtle
but you can notice the next day you're
like oh that's why i feel a little off i
didn't i didn't stick to my schedule of
vitamins do you know off top of your
head what other vitamins you're taking
um i take uh it's elderberry
it's like a little gummy of that and
then i have like a daily vitamin
and then that's kind of it right now i
want to build more onto it though
because like i've definitely
like within last few months like felt
the benefits of like all those vitamins
that i've been taking lately
and i've been like knock on wood or like
whatever i've got around me like i've
been
the healthiest i've been for the longest
like you know i haven't
had anything like a hiccup or like a
sick day or anything like that
so i think it's working and it's
something i want to keep up and like
learn more about but i'm not a
nutritionist
i'm just like here let me start taking
this and then i like start to feel the
benefits of it and i was like okay like
i've
given in to this marketing scheme if
there is one but
yeah i know hats off to you though i
mean for
for taking any any of that stuff though
because it's like we just said it's
super confusing
and uh there's also this aspect you were
just starting to say
you know you get marketed to like your
instagram you start clicking on
you know there's a fish oil ad that
catches your eye and you like read it
for a little while and all of a sudden
all of your ads are about fish oil or
all of your ads are about this new
multivitamin and some of it is like
being sold to us
and and it's kind of you know it's like
is this actually good or is this just
they know the perfect algorithm to get
it in front of me
and they're good at selling it and
making it flashy and making it sound
cool
but if you're taking it and you feel
good then the juice is worth the squeeze
to me
i mean like sell to me if it's gonna
help my health
i think it's for me the oily vitamins
because like all the influencers
end up like getting those or get them
mailed to you the packaging is so pretty
they're on all the like end caps at
target
and so like i'll end up purchasing like
an oily vitamin this is how i got into
the elderberry
and then um but they're like 14.99 it's
only like a month supply so like to me
that's not
a good value i end up buying that like
in the perks of that and then i'll go
find the like
generic brand or like the target brand
or whatever of that vitamin
so i guess they get me in the scheme but
then i'm like nope this isn't worth it
and then i found an alternative way to
get it that's smart though that's that's
what you got to do because
i mean there's so many different
subcategories in different companies and
it gets so confusing so quick i've been
i've been into supplements and stuff for
a long time
um but i still feel like i don't fully
understand
like like i don't know if i need to take
just a full-on
anatomy in in chemistry course into like
human biology and just completely
understand
all of it but i go through phases of
doing all these different vitamins when
i was working out a lot back in the day
i would take a lot of um just like
whatever like i was not careful i wasn't
thinking about my gut lining i wasn't
thinking about like
oh this vitamin reacting with this other
pre-workout pill that i took
or if someone had a you know like a diet
pill and we're gonna go lift or work out
i'd be like cool give me one let's do it
let's let's get our sweat on or whatever
and now i i would never just like take
random stuff i just i have i'm all just
like subtle i have um
i get most of my vitamins from athletic
greens actually
um and i mean you might hear like joe
roach and if you listen to joe rogan all
he advertises for them
um and they're they're really good man i
it makes me feel pretty good that's
usually my shake that i drink
before like 4 or 5 p.m and then that
starts my fast and that has
anti-inflammatory antioxidants
all of your regular vitamins it's like a
multivitamin in there
zinc vitamin vitamin d vitamin c and
then i supplement vitamin d as well
that's probably a great way to like
start off like here's
like giving your body a good kick and
then you know slowly like tapering off
and allowing your body to like do other
things
rather than because like i mean that's
kind of going back to fast and that's
like the big perk of it is that you're
feeding your body all day and all of
your energy is going in
digestion food and not like healing a
different part of your body
that's really smart i've been wanting to
get into collagen lately
but i'm very scared for like how it's
sourced because like i hear all the
great things from it but like where is
it coming from
what are these like animals going
through to like give me this collagen
product and that is something that
yeah that scares me and freaks me out so
to me that's not not worth the benefit
at least yeah not until they find like a
plant-based collagen i guess
yeah yeah i mean you like you don't
really want
there's something about eating food and
in ingesting you know nutrients but
knowing like was this cow just tortured
as it like
before his bones were melted down to
give me the broth
was he completely did he have a terrible
life like what did he eat what were his
bones built off of
and it sounds so silly in in my new but
it i don't know i
i think there is something to be said
when you're drinking these things and
you having
you're having that conscious thought i
was eating buffalo wild wings a couple
weeks ago
um just like a like a sunday or saturday
guilty pleasure thing i was like
i'm getting buffalo wild wings i'm gonna
get a large i'm gonna eat the whole
thing like i was just
i'm gonna go and binge eating again um
but
as i was eating it i started thinking
about
the chickens themselves i started
thinking about like
chickens and cages and i was i was
annoyed because like this is how people
become vegan they start obsessing over
these thoughts of like the
the poor animals and
like i i don't know i just don't have
time to become vegan right now honestly
the the last time we talked i think i
started going into of like how i mean
partially for dietary reasons but also
just like
me being so self-conscious of like where
like what is the impact that this is
like having on earth right now of like
me just like consuming meat
and like i was traveling all over the
country or another country but already
east coast this past few weeks
and the like it was so hard to be
and like keep up with being vegetarian
because like i was out of my routine
and so like i didn't just have my like
whole foods down the road to be able to
go to
like get the things i needed but it was
definitely like an extra added thought
of like oh no where is this stuff coming
from
but like i also had to dismiss it
because i need to like keep my engine
going you know that balance but
we were so the group the the team
the production team i work with we were
kind of like
in a morbid way sort of laughing we were
working on this
at this camp and it's normally like a
student camp
but because of likovid we couldn't like
work in a hotel ballroom
so we had to work at this like random
camp in the middle of nowhere georgia
uh i think it's like called covington
and they have like one target
they have no real grocery stores it's
super sketch but we were on a farm and
the one night we had like really nice
steaks and it was the nicest meal we had
at this camp
the whole entire like four weeks we had
been there um we've been there like off
and on for four weeks and the the camp
food is horrible it's like
cafeteria lunch food but like at the
entrance of the camp it's also a farm
so they have like horses and they have
cows and they have like turkeys that run
around
it's kind of pretty but it is also not
um and so we were all kind of like
morbidly sad
because the last night was steak night
and we're all like the cows that we've
been moo
in at like as we drive in the camp did
one of bertha get killed and now we're
like how fresh is was the steak
cut right like where did we get this
steak from like
why is it so nice in here and they were
like huge pieces of steak like i haven't
been to a steakhouse and gotten this
large piece of steak and we all kind of
like laughed had a moment of silence and
then we kept eating
i mean that's the circle of life that's
that's the actual i mean isn't that
crazy we're so disconnected from our
food
i mean all of us it's just a normal
thing it's not it's not that even
mind-blowing but
we don't think about how our food is
sourced when we're eating it it's just
we're just this thing is in front of me
because i ordered it off the menu and
i'm going to keep talking to my friend
but you don't really think of all the
processes of that's an animal that was
grown
and slaughtered and like how was it
grown what was it fed where was it
growing
what did it eat you know how was it
finished even is
it's a process and then we're ingesting
all those chemicals that they're being
fed to like grow at the speed they need
yeah i think finally people kind of got
woke as the cool kids say to like the
supply chain
and like how we are sourced different
stuff just by like
people went to a grocery store to store
in covid and then like
they didn't have toilet paper and they
didn't understand why but then then you
started reporting on the reasons why
some people started realizing like how
fragile our
food supply chain is or even just like
our common goods
chain of like i mean there were
tornadoes like land hurricanes they
called them
and then that disrupted all of our like
flower supply
and then that like disrupted our bread
and a whole bunch of other things i
think
finally people are realizing that
yeah the inner connectiveness of
our whole world like not just our food
system but it's
it's there you know and everybody knows
it but i think
really as technology expands and as
just our way of getting like all these
exotic foods and
just it's hard as everything expands to
ignore
like oh wow like this is this is all
very connected this is all
you know what i'm eating came from this
other place across the world
and they got food from this other place
across the world and when
you know a land tornado or whatever
happens then i can't
then it affects this and oh the bees and
the honey and
i think that um you know if if you look
at
if you look at flowers for example you
don't see bugs and
bees as a part of the flower
but without without them like what what
are the flowers you know
without it it's just
like our whole world is is so holistic
it it's all connected everything is one
um but it's it we're so disconnected
because it's such a mind-blowing thought
like it's like wait what do what do you
mean like
it's it's all completely all one one big
working
mechanism and and have you seen um uh
i'm so sorry i'm all over the place
megan uh it's fine we're both hopping
around everywhere
we'll have an adhd conversation then i'm
all for it
um have you seen it's a documentary on
netflix will smith is the narrator of it
um one strange rock i think maybe i
think i've heard of it i haven't had
time to watch it yet
yeah oh oh man it's it's so good um it
shows like the
yeah you know the birth of diatoms and
and how
from the from the rain washing over the
rocks
in the amazon rainforest it creates this
which creates this which creates oxygen
which creates
like it like shows you from the
beginning of how
like where our breath comes from where
our oxygen where our co2
all these things how they're born and
how the
certain wind storms in the amazon and
birds eating certain seeds and then
[__] on different sides of the
planet
cause like the good things that happen
in in our atmosphere and
you know it it's super good sounds like
something that would be at my jam
yeah yeah you you would dig it it's it's
a it is visually
beautiful too i mean what the our
cameras nowadays obviously like you know
this very well our cameras nowadays can
give us
these phenomenal visual experiences
and then you have like will smith
narrating it and whoever wrote it is
just a genius too so
it's good one strange rock i think is
what it's called that's great now i'll
check that out
um kind of going along the same thing
something i want to bring up you
mentioned bees
and um there was someone i was briefly
reading an article i didn't have time to
dive into it as much as i wanted to but
they're recently like moving bees
out of one area and they're transporting
all these like hives into like
california
so that way they're able to like
pollinate the stuff that they need to
more because people are like having a
higher demand for like almond milk and
other things that have a high need to be
pollinated in order to grow
and people aren't thinking like oh we
need bees in order to do this to make
our food to make the other things that
you want
and so we're having to like move nature
around just to like make it all work
because it's not doing itself fast
enough to the speed that we need it
right now
right terrifying but also really cool
but terrifying
it is cool i mean it makes sense that
we're at a point where we're going to
as we're one large worldwide ecosystem
we also you know we need to just like we
make our own communities and we're also
a nation
like we almost need to make our own
miniature ecosystems
so we can slow down the the supply chain
like if we can
you know if you're typically waiting on
this product or this thing that's
crucial for your agriculture from china
or some other country or something
if there's a way that you could make it
to where it's completely
self-sustainable within your state
you can provide jobs that way you can
provide you know quicker
quicker transportation you you make it
all right there it's it's like having
having your whole production company
in-house you know it's like
yeah i think people also like like i
said people were worried about it as
like a nation scare here in america
with like early days of covid and us not
getting the things we need
but now the whole entire world just sort
of woke up to the idea as well because
one ship got stuck in
like the canal in egypt i'm not sure if
you saw that on the news it's been stuck
there for a week
and like it hit highway what's on the
ship what like it's
it's like this the ship is like the size
of the empire state building and it's
just a cargo ship like we're not privy
to know like what's on it right now
because it was like uh private i'm
surprised you haven't seen this it's
been all over like everywhere
i know i avoid most news and social
media right now that's smart
so i forget the name of the ship but
it's like stuck
in egypt right now um i actually got
unstuck spoiler alert
but um it was going through the canal
that like all the ships go through to
like
import and export stuff and then it hit
like 40
mile per hour winds and then it turned
and so it blocked the whole entire canal
and it has like
stopped our whole entire cargo and it's
like
yeah like it has stopped our whole
entire
import and export of like all the
countries and so like all these ships
are just built up
and it just got freed this morning um
but they are currently having to like
figure out how to prioritize what
chips can go past the canal first and
then
last um and they're saying that it's
gonna like completely
like change our economic system for a
few months to a few years because
it was costing 400 million dollars an
hour with this like ship being stuck
there
and all the other ships were like stuck
and then
i think because of all the agriculture
ships that were there they like ran out
supplies
to like take care of the animals that
were like in those cargo ships
um that they're like prioritizing those
so that way they can like park and like
feed the animals or whatever they need
to do and then
think about how much food in products
are probably rotting and
expiring you know there's probably a lot
of refrigeration
sort of situations on those so here's a
here's a photo of the ship
that's just like chilling in the canal
and it's completely stuck because it's
like lodged with mud
and so so many people are like trying to
come up with ideas of like how to move
it but they just can't move it
so they had to like just start digging
it out with these like small little
diggers and then people are laughing at
the fact of like all right we have this
small little
like construction digger thing and it's
like trying to
move this ship that's um like the size
of the empire state building but that
wasn't the case they were just trying to
like dig out the mud so that way they
could like
tug it one way and the other yeah just
get it straight so then it could go
but yeah but it halted all of our import
and export so like
this will probably change the fashion
industry for a while it might change
like
toilet paper again and paper towels and
like cause everything to be a little bit
more expensive
but like you and i will probably see it
like a minute level but
i mean i i need all my organic stuff man
i better not slow that down no i don't
think that's coming from china if it
well
no probably not in your side of the
country it's coming from china
yeah that's that's farther wow that's
intense they should have hired us they
should have hired a
a good production company who works good
under pressure
those were my favorite memes during like
coven of like hey
why don't we just hire production
companies to like manage the test
insights like
it'd be done in a week and then they'd
be out and cleared and coven would be
completely gone yeah we'll get it you
just tell us what to do we'll get in
there we'll set it up
we'll run the whole thing it'll go
really quick we're really good on our
feet we're really good at live
troubleshooting and then we'll just take
it down in a half a day and you'll
you'll not see a trace of us
yeah it'll be cheaper people will be
entertained
you know right we'll fly in pitbull
yeah he'll be on like a little stage as
people are getting vaccinated
mr worldwide is just performing in
concert oh my gosh
like an entire kid rock it was um so the
hotel that we were at
this past week for the show it was
really weird because it was just like
students and like you know 11 students i
guess
and then us as a production team and
then all these military people
and it's because red cross street was
like a fema site for
um covetous encoded vaccines so they had
like all the military people just like
living in our hotel and that felt a
little weird being
because like you're normally in a hotel
and it's just like vacationers and stuff
but then you have like all these like
very sharp like proper walking military
people and it's like how serious is this
and we're just like having our like
little show downstairs
you're like can i wear jeans in the
lobby or right
it's less casual the line at the coffee
shop would also be like crazy long
because they all had um
like vouchers to get their breakfast i
guess that's like
how they were supplying all their food
for the military people that was a
little weird
anyway we are all over the place on this
conversation
honestly dude people get it like if
people are still listening this is like
my
like almost 75th episode so i feel like
at this point people get it's
crazy hd yeah it's quite a few it's uh
it's it's interesting i wonder like if
covet didn't happen
i want i feel like i'd be at like 150 if
if covet didn't happen
because i i mean i had the old studio
and i had people coming in
um but but i i don't know i i am growing
to like zoom
you know i like having the the video
done for me
is nice too and i'm also i didn't think
that i would be able to connect with
people as well as i do on here like i
thought as soon as it went as
soon as we went to coven and like people
are going to zoom i was like
there's no way that i could hold my
attention for that long there's no way
that i can like connect with people and
like really get their vibe but
honestly it's it's worked out way better
than i thought so far i've had some
really good conversations on zoom
i think it would be i think we've been
able to connect more people
together because of like zoom and stuff
like you and i wouldn't be sitting
together like having a podcast unless i
came over to your side of the country
you know sitting here in florida and
then
like we wouldn't have had like an
in-person uh
podcast session or even like abrielle or
tyler
like you've been able to connect to so
many more people yeah yeah i think it i
think it challenges me too
to you know because like starting
starting the podcast
um i was i was very aware
of like hey i'm not you know i'm not
like
a qualified news reporter like i haven't
been doing something like this for a
long time
i'm comfortable with the mic in my hand
i've done stage work i've done dj stuff
i've done acting stuff
but i'm not i mean podcasting for
talking for you know three four hours at
a time sometimes
is a skill that kind of needs built up
so at the beginning
i pretty much had you know i'm friends
with a lot of people like a lot of
really cool people and so i was able to
just
you know hit these people up who live in
my same hometown who
are you know it's just me talking to my
friend but i can bring them on
and kind of like dig into their story
and like show other people
what's what i already know is really
cool about them so it was like a very
comfortable
start for me you know i think i think
it's i'm gonna be
you know as i continue to do this over
over the years or whatever i end up
doing
i'm gonna be very grateful for my first
you know like 50 episodes for sure
you know 60 episodes because it was a
lot of my friends willing to come on
here and kind of let me just
blab my way through and try to like be a
good host to learn what being a host is
about you know and so
now now i'm just getting better and more
more comfortable with with new people
and um you know i'll get kind of random
random emails or like a podcast agent
will
will reach out to me to connect me to
somebody else um and now i'm like yeah
let's let's do it i don't know
i have never met this person but i think
that'd be a good conversation let's do
it so yeah then you can learn more about
people
i think yeah i was having a conversation
with um one of our announcer people
that our production company we hire
and um him and i we have like very
different views
on a lot of different things and a lot
of people were
mentioned like how they were intimidated
like him coming even in like our little
pot on set just because
like he is very vocal about his opposite
like political views and like world
views and stuff
and for me i was like him and i'm really
good friends and it's like i'm not
i see this stuff too like i'm not gonna
let that change like my opinion on that
person but
i really wanted to sit down while we
were on a show
and like conversate with that person
just so that way i could like understand
why he
believed all the things that he did and
like his viewpoint on all these like
worldly things
and then like i could like grow on that
side and we like sat down
we talked for a few hours we like sort
of laid it all out oh yeah
um did you guys connect like did you see
eye to eye
uh i don't i think we just like
respected each other's opinion like we
were very
open about like each other's opinion on
like how different
both of us were of certain things and
like we were both very adults and like
we didn't allow it to be like too
personal but we both like just explained
to each other why we had these opinions
on this sort of like side of it
and i think somehow we both sort of come
closer to like a middle
ground point because i understood a lot
more of like because of you know he was
in a california state
and um they're like super you know
panoramic uh conscious you know call it
panoramic that's what the cool kids call
it now um but you know they're like
giving people tickets for
you know being out in the street and
like not wearing masks and stuff and
then
like i'm here in florida where it's like
open gates
and so like him and i were able to like
kind of come more to like a middle
ground of like
this is you know maybe a different idea
of like coming things but
like what i'm trying to get at is i
think it's like
the greatest benefit of like you having
a podcast
is like you getting to be exposed to
more people that like have different
thoughts and are like have
grown in different ways and like just
being like a little person that like
lives in your house you don't always
have those
like abilities to like meet all those
people but like people can
i believe people grow by talking from
and with other people and like
enjoying their experiences and then you
get to
like learn about a whole different life
that like someone else's live in and
like the things that they've learned and
then try to apply to their life
but so many people are like closed
minded from trying to do that and like
wanting to have conversations because
they
just try and like throw their their
opinions and views on other people and
they're so like stuck in the mud
on those ideas that they can't like
change but right
people need to be open and like learn
from them
yeah i mean that's super cool that you
that you guys sat down and just had like
an open conversation knowing you went
into it knowing we have differing
beliefs
but you also outside of those beliefs
you know like
like if if the politics or the coveted
situation wasn't around
it's like someone that you get along
with just fine so
it's it's like hey i respect you just as
a person we've always had great
conversation we've always had nice
interactions we've been kind of friends
or whatever
but there is this side that i think that
we have differing beliefs on and for you
to be able to say i respect you but i
would love to have this conversation
and then him to also reciprocate that's
so cool and that's what the world needs
so much like the dude that's the power
of conversation
it's i mean it's it's literally
what we are as humanity like if we
didn't have language if we didn't talk
through things
if we didn't work together find ways to
to vocally work together so we can
physically work together and create
things
in create society and build skyscrapers
and
whatever i mean that this wouldn't work
if we if we didn't have a conversation
so i think that
um you know in our our very divided
world we have here
you know with i think a lot of us
sitting in our homes not talking to a
lot of people not reaching out to
different people just scrolling
yeah we're literally getting our our
view of how the world
is is painted by news media it's painted
by
these are you know companies let's say
six companies who own all these major
news sites
um you know not to mention all the
alternative media on youtube and stuff
but
there's our view of
other people or people of differing
beliefs is painted for us
and so we're kind of left up to like hey
that
that doesn't seem i don't agree with
with what that person says but then
we're kind of left up to
how do we handle that in in real life
you know if you so you're able to say
hey i know that you're a person who has
different beliefs in me
but i know that but because i know you i
know that doesn't mean that you you know
hate
these whole the all these people or
you're blue so you hate all the red or
whatever what do you really
mean here and that alone just saying hey
what what do you think about this
and having someone with their physical
presence or even over a zoom
call they're there you can hear their
vocal tonality
you can hear their cadence it's not
typed up
it's not presented in this in this
tricky way to make you an enemy or a bad
other
you know it's it's important
conversation is
one of the most important tools that we
have for keeping our sanity as humanity
yeah and even like you saying that like
oh we only have like six
um you know a certain amount of like
news sites that are all like pumping us
our information like a lot of people are
also getting their information off
social media
and the social media is like creating an
algorithm and they know what you're
going to click on
and they know what is going to like get
you going to like get a view
and so you were also all being just
painted the like
the dialogue that like our social media
channels
also think that we want to see so then
that becomes like our
alternative juice um my mom and i who
like
i mean we you know i was raised by her
so obviously
i would have similar or a greater
understanding of like her beliefs
because of that
um we both like follow similar news
channels and stuff
on social media and she was being
painted one picture of like certain
situations
of you know a lot of stuff that was
going on last summer and then my social
media
also like you know an age difference i
was being painted a completely different
um sort of like dialogue on social media
so the two of us i was like no that's
that's not quite right that's not
what i had seen and so like we would
have to like sit there with like our
seats
and like try and figure out you know
what the our troops were
like our understanding of what was
actually happening so
but like again if all these people that
are just texting at home right now
and not having these like resume calls
or like you know calling up people and
being willing to like
talk about hard just you know topics
without becoming upset with that other
person
like we all become just like whatever
our phones sort of
are and like whatever our phones are
telling us which is sort of like
a lot of the heat of a lot of the issues
that are going on right now
all the anger so much anger yeah i mean
well it's because we're meeting people
okay so like you know we we've we've
worked together quite a few times we've
been friends for for
quite a few years um i like
what what like if you knew
okay how do i paint this essentially
where we're meeting people at their
worst traits
like where where a picture is being
being painted
about someone and so when you see
you know like we all have an
uncle who we love but he's kind of a
dick you know you know
or you know your grandpa he's just old
old-fashioned like he says some things
that you'd be like
grandpa you can't say that [__] but you
know him you love him you know he has he
has good intentions
and you don't think all he is is just
this political side he's just you know
team red or team blue or whatever it is
you know but
the news media kind of makes us meet
people there
first you know not you're you're my
grandpa or you're my friend
you're a person that i know here's the
things that i like about you
hey and then also like so oh okay so we
do have different opinions on that
whatever you know that's healthy
but what the news does and what it makes
us accidentally do
because we're all in this fear response
right our brains
our brain stem is activated we
immediately seeing new people meeting
new people or even
our our old friends you know facebook is
a is a war nowadays
um where we we now meet them at their
worst traits
so like if if you liked me but the first
time you meet me you have to read
a five minute list of every bad thing
i've ever done
like what that's not how you meet a
person because we're so much more
intricate than that you know
i think what we have in each moment is
is who we show up as
in in the moment like if you can be kind
if you can
if you can listen um if you can you know
police yourself in a way and try to
watch your emotions and
you know you could have very differing
opinions and have a
long beautiful respectable conversation
with the person across from you
and then both will like come out
hopefully learning something about not
any other person but also just like
like how the other person has lived and
like how people
are out there living and what their
struggles are mm-hmm
i think have you have you always been
been like open
in reciprocal to you know like
new ideas um like like wanting to i mean
because it's unusual not a lot of people
would
would know oh this person that i work
with has very different companions of me
um most of the time it's kind of awkward
or maybe you avoid it or you don't say
anything or whatever but you're like i
want to talk to him like let's let's get
to the bottom of this let's see what our
differences are
that's an unusual trait trait to have um
have you always had that
i think only with the right people
because like i could probably count on
like
within my two hands of like the amount
of people that i can
have a healthy conversation with and i
think it a lot of it is built on
the amount that like i know that person
and know that like okay
by me talking with this person i know
that like i'm in safe spaces
and this person isn't gonna like hate me
or like if an employer is gonna like ban
me or something because like i wanna
have this conversation with someone
so i think it's like only if i know that
like that person could have that
conversation with me as well and that we
both gonna like walk away from it
like the same way that we not the same
way but like have the same relationship
as we did going into it and i think
finding those people are extremely rare
i don't but those are also some of my
favorite people to talk to because we
could probably talk for hours and then
just like go on about all the worldly
things and then like i learn and they
learn
and it's it's really cool those are
special relationships to have with those
people
yeah yes because you get to meet you
again you
you meet on the level of i respect you
already like i know
you're not gonna i'm not gonna have this
conversation you're gonna try to rip me
apart
or be disrespectful to me you know right
like is it gonna be an argument or an
actual conversation
yeah it's like i mean my mom and i like
we even just start arguing like there's
a lot of times where it's like hey mom
we can't we we're not talking politics
like we just we can't do it and it's
like
you know i think it's also like the
nature of the energy that you bring to
the conversation so
some people seem very on social media
they'll seem very like
angry but like i know that person in
real life so it's like i don't think
that person's actually that angry what's
up i don't know i want to
talk with them it was great yeah i i
like that example i i have a couple
friends who
i would say i mean even me actually
probably like i probably come off pretty
intense on social media some of the
things that i that i write out but i
have friends that
they like well if i didn't know them
outside of social media i would be
scrolling and be like that guy's a prick
you know like because they'll just say
they're very obtuse or very you know
um but but i think that kind of speaks
to the nature of social media right
we're all kind of like
like bantering and we're all kind of
pandering to our group
in unconscious ways or like what we post
and what we say is very policed by us
you know we're very
tiptoeing because we're not trying to
have the arguments but some people are
like
full-on [__] you if you think this like
you know full-on just i'm gonna i'm
gonna post everything and if
and my enemies will show their faces you
know which is
man so i think overall social media we
just don't really know how
how we can't understand how different
social media interaction is from
actual face to face listening to
someone's voice
saying oh it's crazy because it's just a
filter like i hate to use word filter
but like it is a
filtered version of all of us it's
either the like really pretty stuff or
the like
very vocal like trying to be an activist
sort of
a thing and i love watching social media
documentaries and talking about like
how is this just like disrupting all of
us as people because like
we all used to be very like community
like whatever
our social network right was everything
that was like in our
like demographic like everything that
was you know a few miles away or like
always seeing the same people at the
supermarket
and like that's how you interact with
people and like growing up
in pittsburgh up in pennsylvania like
that's how our town was it was very like
very small everybody knew everybody like
everybody sat the same pew and church
and stuff
and then like moving to florida a
completely different world but like
people were just not as connected
and then i was growing up on social
media and then that's like
just how everybody connected so like the
kids that are grown up now that that's
their only way that they're connected
and they're grown up from
parents that are our generation that
mainly connect with their other friends
and stuff through social media
what are their like social skills going
to be like like how are we just
completely disrupting
like human species with this
like internet capability it's crazy
oh oh i mean i mean totally i think our
i mean because i think of i've done a
lot in the last couple years i've done a
lot of um
you know studying and like kind of just
diving into
um
even things like confidence in like
how you so so okay so people being on
their phones and not having face-to-face
conversations like me when i was younger
growing up i'm naturally more
introverted person
but just life circumstances
i kind of had to learn how to like all
right i need to fit in in this situation
so i start watching people i start like
okay that's how that person reacts you
know that's
okay is that person standing like this
all right you know you're looking at
like the hierarchy of how
social interactions work all the time i
feel so like
okay keep going you also do this like
you're observant of how other people
yeah hey you could be a dj um but uh
it's you know all the these skills that
they were difficult and they were
uncomfortable for me and especially you
know when i turned
turned 15 16 i remember going into the
clothing store that i first worked at
when i when i turned 16
and i would go in and i would i
convinced the manager to let me pretend
that i worked there so i could sell to
people because i wanted a job there like
in a few months
so forcing myself out of my comfort zone
like that wasn't a
it might have like seemed natural
because i was overly caught i was very
confident in that in myself because i
had been like studying people in a way
um but having those social skills to go
up to someone and start selling to them
and talking to a complete stranger
nowadays not there's a lot of younger
generation who don't have that
like it's actually it's it's
nerve-wracking for them um because
they're so used to their their life
and this is not an insult this is not
like this is just
noticing there is huge differences in
the way that our generation
um like we're not even like we're around
the age 30. like we're not even that old
and just these younger kids now they
have a completely different view of
reality and we even grew up with some
sort of social media so
um there's a lot of so
if you're depressed for example like
megan if i was asking you
if you if i said if i was describing a
depressed person
what would their shoulders be like like
what would they be maybe slumped over
would they be kind of like forward a
little bit you know maybe you picture
someone with a hood on
you know they're just it's like i'm kind
of depressed i'm feeling under the
weather you're not open your chest isn't
open but if you're confident
your shoulders are back your chest is
open um
this actually releases serotonin
throughout your body
lobsters for example the highest lobster
in the hierarchy
is the one who has the most upright
posture and he rises to the top of the
tank
but so we've done experience experiments
with
like serotonin and ssri inhibitors and
antidepressants and stuff
with lobsters um to like kind of
like prove a lot of our our social
hierarchy has a lot to do with our
our depression and our like anxieties
and those sorts of things
so what i think what i'm what i'm
rounding about
is i think that we're going to have many
negative social aspects that affect the
individual
on a biochemical level from having just
interaction through our phones
you know not not being able to to
conversate or talk with people or
respond when someone approaches you
without getting extreme social anxiety
and again these are nothing to be
ashamed of you know
this is some social anxiety is something
a lot of people go through it's going to
be in the next 10 years
like millions of people are going to
have real serious hurdles to overcome
with social anxiety and
you know lacks lack of confidence in in
physical interactions
right but like even something you just
said just sort of like scared me in a
way because you said what does a
depressed person look like
but we also live in a world where like
we can mask that so easily
like we go out and you know when we are
in person like we have to
like appear happy because we're at work
or something or
where and you know it's like almost not
okay to like seem sad or something
because that's so
jarring to so many people whereas also
on social media we're able to just like
post a photo of us like looking happy
for a few seconds and then again
we all appear happy so like that's even
more triggering and a deeper thought of
like
what does a depressed person look like
anymore because we don't always see
people
in their like truest form that they're
actually giving off
that's so true yeah i mean so that's
it's going to be up to us as individuals
to
notice like oh man my shoulders are slim
forward like i'm kind of
giving into this you know i'm not i'm
not open and
you know open to receiving the
conversation that that's coming at me
and and it is interesting thinking you
know
like like if you were to bring your top
10 friends on
that you have on social media that you
like kind of interact with you like
their pictures whatever you just have
interactions with them
if if you had to think of your top 10
friends you'd probably say oh and you
know they're doing pretty good i just
saw them oh yeah you know
ashley just got a new house um sarah
sarah just she just posted this photo
with her and her family it's great
you know but at this moment you could
you know that means five days ago or
something at this moment they could be
extremely depressed they could be
eating their second thing thing of ice
cream because they're really feeling
some self-shame
you know they you they maybe they're
maybe they're sad maybe they're going
through a breakup like there's so
many humans are so complicated but
there's something about social media
that paints it to where
it's like oh i'm saying i'm all good i'm
perfect i'm
i'm all good and we we read it kind of
like that i think we do that with famous
people too we see them on social media
or
or on their on their life and we're like
oh what do you have to complain about
you're in a [__] mansion
but i mean they're real people you know
and they they have emotions too they
might literally deal with extreme
depression but they're trying to
make sure their avatar their image
that's given to the world
is that same person because they have a
career to take care of and
oh my gosh that rules like right into
like cancel culture too because like
you know some people's whole entire
world is
like just uploading content on the
internet and then if as soon as like a
cancel culture moment happens or if they
like pull out
like it's extremely noticed or they
start to like fall back into it
that's also a really interesting concept
yeah
i mean what what a split in our psyche
for real what what do you think about
cancer culture i i was planning on
having um
my friend spencer who i've done a couple
of um like more serious like
hey the the world is losing its mind
let's try to get to the bottom of why
sort of conversations we are going to
have
a cancel culture conversation and i
think that him and i actually are on
differing sides
i think canceled culture is crap and he
he thinks that it's
like an important thing but he's also
very intelligent so i'm
gonna of course listen to everything he
has to say and i love having the
conversations with him
um but what what do you what's your
views on canceled culture like what do
you think about so i guess i said one
with you because i also think it's
it's kind of crap um just because uh a
great something i've been following
very closely and like maybe trigger
warning here um
but it's like david dobrik i'm not sure
if you've been in the news with him but
he's part of
he's part of the vlog squad um which is
like this
it was kind of um like an internet house
before it was an internet house and
a house is where it's like a creator
place where
like a group of creators sort of all
like join together
and they're all creating stuff on their
separate channels but then they're also
creating stuff on like a larger channel
so david dobrik um he's a young person i
think he's
like 22 maybe 23. he's very young um
he has a large mansion and he sort of
came out from the bottom he started off
as like a viner
and then he's like just sort of grown up
from there and also like really grown up
with social media
well turns out a few years ago one
person that was in the very early days
of the vlog squad took advantage of
a female and they sort of like made that
a video
and he's known for making really short
like four minutes and 20 second long
videos that get uploaded youtube
and then that sort of like you know
david's vlogs so
she just recently wrote a letter about
how somebody else
that was in the vlog squad that is no
longer in a vlog squad because
he no longer wants to sushi himself with
that sort of
a person and he was known as i think his
name was dirty dave
something along those lines was the name
of this guy like
he was he was very not okay even in
the early days of the internet because
like early days internet was sort of
like raunchy very
wild with yeah yeah sexual racist
in a lot of ways as well um but because
of all of this
david has written again he's like
completely changed his platform
um he's very big about making sure that
everybody in his videos are like consent
into the video that they're
uploading or that he's uploading he has
like everybody watch it before he pushes
play
or pushes upload and like it's
completely wrecking his whole entire
life because this woman said that
she was taken advantage by a former
member of vlog squad
and he's lost all of his um all of his
sponsorships like he was probably like
hello fresh
um a few other ones seat geek i think
even had to like make a statement about
it
he's no longer doing his podcast he's
lost his
um reality show that he was hosting
like he was on the train to be like the
next like jimmy fallon or something like
that and that's what he wanted to do
and now his whole entire life is just
like wrecked because of like somebody
something that somebody else did that
was like odin days
you know david and it's like that is not
okay like you are now reckon
like and it's not even the letter that
was originally written in the article
that
the girl had you know made public it's
like
it's now all the fans are like taken
upon themselves
to wreck this successful person's life
and it's like that's their career
that's a whole bunch of other people's
jobs and you just like
turn it upside down and it's like yeah
that's someone's livelihood man that's
someone's job
like that you don't dude
we're doing this weird thing you know i
had in my conversation with abraham i
was talking about this wwe reality that
we're feeding into um
and it's like this overlay of we're
almost
instead of believing what we actually
believe or like wondering like
oh okay like what do i really think
about that and really giving it a few
minutes to
to contemplate like okay i know people
who have done weird things i know people
who
have um you know that i don't affiliate
with anymore who have have done things
or
i've done things in the past that i'm
not proud of but like i don't do them
anymore because i learn that's what
humans do we grow and we learn and we
we get more mature as we age but i think
that
i wonder if what we're doing a lot with
social media in a very unconscious way
is worth signaling
like all of his fans all of his all of
the
companies who are dropping they're
basically signaling like hey we don't
we we don't condone that that's what
we're like this is what we're saying by
by dropping in is we don't condone that
when realistically we should
maybe we we don't have to skip over
these things maybe this could have been
like a
you know a one very serious day of press
release for him and his team to be like
listen here's the situation from our
perspective here's what happened
here's what we do now here's how we
approach things differently
because we've grown because that's what
humans do okay
now let's stop talking about it if you
want to be my fan be my fan let's go if
not
like i respect your right to leave it it
needs to
we need to our problem solving i mean
what if we did this in real life like
what if
we're all working a show we're on a
week-long show and
one of the days you come because you've
had a bad day and you you know
you maybe you're not in a bat or in a
good mood and you kind of like
snap on someone what if we all get
together and we're like megan you need
to go over there
we're gonna have this conversation to
talk about your future and we all just
decide like hey we don't
we don't condone uh people being
aggressive
so to prove that we need to fire megan
and we need to call all of our future
employers
and we need to burn her and we need to
shake a
shame stick at her to make sure nobody
else ever likes her ever again
and we need to make public statements
yeah i mean even making public
statements is is something that like
should we have to do it just because
someone brings up something from our
past
i mean i i just don't i think it's the
most waste of time [__] ever is what
i think
i think okay so what what are what what
would you say are some benefits is there
any benefits to cancel culture
like this situation with him with david
or whatever that seems like
completely nonsense but yeah he's like
i mean he's unrelated related to it but
like
i don't know i've seen it so much within
the last like five or six
years and like i hate to say it but like
cancel culture
started when the whole entire like me
too movement was really pushing through
and that that can get on a different
topic but the
like so many people are so quick that
they are angered at a person
and it will make i mean in this case in
david's case the
accusations i mean there's video proof
are
are very true but it's not even against
david it's just old people who is
associated with but anytime someone's
like even angry at somebody they'll make
all these like false claims
and then like try and go public with it
or start tweeting
and using social media as like a
platform to like try and cancel people
and i think like if you are actually a
bad person those are the things that
do need to shine through but it's oh
again kanto culture is just a way of
like
trying to get a whole bunch of people to
turn against these people
and then it turns out that they don't
get the update when it's like okay this
person's name was cleared like these
people are never with
anyone um the host of the talking dead
i'm really bad with
names so i forget it um he adorned
the [__] dead host i gotta google
this because i need to know the name
um chris hard hardwick is his name and
he
was host of talking dead and he was
doing a few other things as well
and someone came out and made all these
like
false accusations of him and right then
and there he lost four of his main tv
show deals
um like no one even like took a thought
of like checking in with the other
person
like hey man like what's up it was real
quick of like we're just gonna drop you
across the board
his wife was even like i don't i don't
think this is possible
like like she had to make statements for
it and then it
came out that um because like he's known
as like a good guy
at least publicly that yeah the lady was
lying
and then you know she he was fine he got
all his deals back but like how many
people didn't get that update
because they weren't in the like height
of the moment when it was cancelled
followers right and so it never comes
back of like oh okay this person's like
okay again like continue to follow them
because again like we only know
what the internet versions of these
people are like we
these people are so famous that they're
almost like unreachable that we don't
get a moment to actually know
who they are in their character only
what is posted and so when
cancelled culture starts to arise and
then we don't
like we only know the like face value of
all these people
so then we like wait to see if these
people are actually like
who they sold themselves to be which is
i think the like root of cancelled
culture
right i'm i mean i think that that's a
huge part that you're saying though is
i feel like the initial breaking story
is the biggest deal
i mean what you first hear i mean
suddenly
you know if there's like the david thing
i'm sure a lot of people
a lot more people know about the
breaking news like oh he's associated
with this blah blah
and that'll stick in their heads like
people who don't care about him or like
don't know about him or like don't
really watch him whatever
in two months as as like a casual izzy
casually comes up in a conversation they
might be like oh yeah didn't he like
was he involved with some girl years ago
or where you know that's the thing that
we remember the breaking news story
the first thing that's often the lie to
sell
clicks or to sell you know like let's
let's ruin this person's life so we can
have
five days of fame for for for this other
person or whatever
um it like our because our attention
span
like because when i read something like
that i'm not going to set an alarm my
phone to be like all right let's make
sure i'm going to check this story in
five days
to make sure that it wasn't disproved
wrong so i can change my internal
opinion
we don't have time for that like we're
just consuming so much new stuff
i mean a week later we're on to the next
thing and now we've just kind of had
that one little memory of that whole
person
and it's not fair to those people it's
not fair for them to have
their whole you know projected
you know life really to just be suddenly
cut off
the head cut off he lost all of his
sponsors and stuff because of
um an accusation or you know it's right
and and also
i think i think we have to look at
podcasts
and um this like this connectivity like
the fact that we're able to connect i
mean you're in florida i'm in washington
right now
that's pretty profound we're already
just super used to it that stuff helps
us grow as humans
like every conversation that i have i
become more mature every interaction
that i have and as i grow as a man i
change and i
and i develop in different ways so in an
interview if someone's like
tries to catch me off guard or they try
to come at me or they try to cancel me
or whatever like here's the thing that
happened to you here's the thing you
said or here's the thing you did
this many years ago and i'll be like
i'll probably just be like
yeah you know i don't owe you an
explanation but let's talk about it
you know here's here's that's who i was
back then and here's why and here's the
troubles that i had
but who i am today is this because we
have to have
room for growth as individuals as as
adults because that's
literally what humans do we're here to
grow and evolve
and learn through experience and and um
you know
and i'm not trying you know there is
there is shitty people who have done
shitty things
who have totally false um you know
repentance and false you know they don't
they don't feel bad or they haven't
actually learned from their mistakes or
whatever it is
that exists but i don't know cancer
culture is just
garbage dude right and it always seems
to like trigger
at certain times like this kid's like 23
so like i mean
he was probably 19 19 20 when this vlog
went out because it was two or three
years ago
and it's like he just made it like he
just got like hosting status of the tv
show he just bought a 19 million dollar
house
and it's always like whenever a certain
rise or like point of fame hits
that all of a sudden it seems to like
crumble because like
someone that you were associated years
ago with like did something
and then a person decides to come out
and just like
like he found about out about this whole
entire claim the same moment that the
wrestler
did because this hannah girl i'm not
sure if that's her real name or that's
the name she's going by
um like decide to go to a news
organization that of course would love a
david dobrik story because he's very
like hot in the internet world right now
and then just decided to probably got
like a payout for it even
to write this news article and then
you know go public with it but like
i mean again this is like edging on
other topics like
it sounds like something that needs to
have been done privately like yes like
you know go after this person you know
they did something to you that you now
feel
they need to do something against but
like go after
uh dirty dave or dirty dan don't go
after like david dobrik he didn't
yeah he really didn't do anything yeah
you're coming after david dobrik because
he now has something that you can take
right i mean i think i think hannah's
peanut butter and jealous
i think that's what's going on she's
like i don't i don't have much
i'm just working at kfc like i don't
have a mansion and i remember this thing
that's upsetting me it's been upset i
mean that guy was involved he was there
he was
he was around he knows the guy that hurt
me you know it's it's just the incorrect
way you're right it's the incorrect way
to go about it
like her feelings and her claims are
very valid but it's just like
now the fans are all like cancel that he
has like a quick big hoodie and so it's
like cancel like click bait and like
cancel the podcast and go after all
these other people and it's like
not a lot of people have other claims
it's not like you know
tiger woods who's like coming out and
has like a laundry list of like claims
going after
people to like prove the character of
this person like
david but yeah canceled culture like
upsets me a lot because then this like
creator that i really like and like has
really good content and there's a lot of
different people all of a sudden it's
just like
destroyed and can't even make content
anymore because
like they can't afford to you know stop
whatever
other income that they have coming in to
go back and create in videos or like
create whatever content they were making
because like we destroyed their life
yeah
it doesn't make any sense it's really um
did you hear about the the ellen
degeneres cancel thing
it was like a little bit ago so so i
don't know a ton about it so
if if i if i misspeak or i'm misinformed
definitely correct me
if you know more but um so my
understanding is that she was like
you know because her image the character
that we see as ellen because
just like dwayne the rock johnson is not
the rock at all times
like he's playing a character when he's
on stage ellen has like she shows up as
this very genuine
sweet sweet person you know and she's
she's very kind and she's very giving
her show has done so much good she's
helped so many people
given thousands millions of dollars
helped crazy amounts of animals like
ellen has
done a lot of good and then she was
about to be canceled or starting to be
cancelled because
she snapped it like someone backstage or
she was rude kind of rude to someone
and it's like hold up do you have any
idea what humans are like have you ever
been rude to someone oh you have
that's because you're a person so is
ellen degeneres like she can't be
on all the time i mean it doesn't make
any sense
like like to me when i saw that story i
remember
because i really like ellen degeneres i
i like i feel like as a host i kind of
like halfway study her i think
the way she interacts with humans is is
she's very
she's very like people what she's done
to like change the
like image of you know lgbt community in
the public eyes like various plots i
love it oh yeah i mean
way back in the day when she was a
comedian um like when she came out as
a lesbian woman like that was that was
one of those things where like
back then it was not okay and like she
got dropped from a bunch of stuff
and like she like had to basically
restart her life over and like re-dig
herself
up as that from her career at that point
i mean
she's a legend and she's done so much
good to me
i don't understand how how does every
all the good that she's done
how does that not like balance out like
oh she was really mean
and and so all of a sudden it cancels
all that good like [__] all those
animals she saved
[__] all those you know millions of
dollars that she donates to these people
all the the people that she's made feel
genuine joy like that doesn't matter
that has no
balance to weigh against the fact that
she yelled at me in that meeting
because of of workplace issues which
like we've had bosses that
like suck as business people that are
like really good
humans like when you get to know them
and it's just like if you
they're like ellen is running around as
like a as a company and as a
you know as a manager of in a sense of
like her whole entire
uh image really and yeah you're gonna
catch her at moments or like
get caught at the wrong moment with like
a production assistant and you know
she's just angry because of like
something else that's going on
you know again with ella know that the
reason why she was like getting cancer
in that moment was because it was an
image thing she does do so many good
things but then to find out from a few
people that like
their workplace environment isn't 100
but i think i mean that could have gone
real south real quick
ellen's thing but i think she handled
that in a
in a way and she was also caught up in
that limelight when
that was again a really hot topic was to
destroy people in like workplace and
you know sort of claims but yeah as you
said she's a human that was a work
situation where she goes at managers
like
a lot's on a line like she has a lot of
jobs that she has to like
keep up for people yeah no doubt and it
just seems like
you know just because her show's public
doesn't mean that all her dirty laundry
should be public
you know like that's another thing i
think that that should have stayed
internal
i don't you know again like i i don't
know the the details and like maybe
maybe ellen said some like really mean
[__] or she
like was continuously mean to people and
maybe that means like
you keep it internal and you say you
know you you point it out to ellen or
somebody i don't know there's there's so
many different things that could happen
then
the person who's disgruntled tries to
tear down the person with
with the fame and recognition and like
oh because i know them
i know who they really are it's like
that's not a real sentence you dick
that's like that's not how people work
people have bad days people do bad
things like people
have to you know stumble over some stuff
once in a while so they can
learn to to look out for it in the
future you know we've
we've got to have room to grow and i'm
not making excuses like like that
doesn't mean you could do
shitty stuff and say you're sorry
afterwards and it's all good that's not
how life works either but
it's just it just seems so to me with
the cancel culture stuff i remember
watching
ellen's apology for it and i was just
i was on the other i'm just watching it
going like what why is she doing this
like don't waste your time just i feel
like we should ignore this stuff
i feel like we should just stop because
it gets us we see it and we're like oh
ellen did this oh wow
but but i want to stop even like feeding
into that i want to be like
that's probably untrue and like i i
don't care about it what i don't it just
seems like of all the things that we're
spending our 24 hours of day on
like what we're focusing on why aren't
we talking about like
the environment breaking down why aren't
we talking about like way more
important things like how do we keep our
sanity as social media
is is increasing in use like there's
just millions of other things that we
can be talking about than
other people's dirty laundry or their
side steps or their mistakes or
it just seems very non-helpful to
[__] anything
it also seems that we always get caught
up on the like like we always blow up
the smaller things and then negate the
larger things when like someone actually
does something
horrible and you know they're now on
like try actual trial for it not just
like social trial
but like actual trial for will often
like push those aside because those
aren't the trendy things to talk
about in that moment but then like you
know
when someone yells at a co-worker or
you know some bad workplace stuff
happens that's the stuff that explodes
and again like we see ellen all the time
on social media like her video popped up
for both of us
but like we don't see you know except
for a very graphic way by like you know
peter or something but we don't see
the like environmental things that are
happening
that are you know going out there it's
because we don't even really know
if you know having like a land hurricane
is a fault of like our environment or if
that's just a natural thing but those
aren't the things that will get like put
in the limelight
so those aren't the like hot topics for
us to like cancel like we're not gonna
like how do you cancel how do you cancel
uh
you know global warming or like global
change because
of emissions when you can't really see
that to like make a post about it to
like prove it to people some people
don't believe it's real
that change is real global warming who
knows but yeah
i mean it almost seems like we're just
doing this very high school
low hanging through like what what's the
easiest thing that we could all come
together and argue about like
oh so-and-so said this oh
i saw so-and-so texting this like like
it just seems so juvenile that we spend
that i mean but i guess that's kind of
what social media
is in a lot of ways like not not
entirely it's not
certainly not completely that but it
does have
it's it is very easily like pulled into
the high school way of viewing things
or even you know if i look at um
snapchat's social media that i still
or wait i deleted the app yesterday okay
so so snapchat i would watch
i've been i've been trying to get off
social media a little bit i had i had
snapchat
because i only had like 15 friends on
there and they were kind of close to
friends so i wanted to like
i don't know um but if you look at the
discover page
just looking at the headlines like the
four words of you know
um kim reveals the real truth of why her
and kanye got a divorce or
so and so like it's these click bait but
it's it's beyond clickbait they're
painting a picture of an entire scenario
for us to interact with and it's
enticing
it's weird because it's it's something
where you're you're like i don't give a
[__] about that but then sometimes
you're like
i'm gonna click on it though you know
and and we play into this
really low dumb emotional level
of of seeing problems and we kind of
don't take it serious
we take it as this joke it's this fun
entertainment for us it's it's playing
on the slide
the slot machine of our iphone but
that's real people in the real life on
the other side of that and they deserve
respect you know they deserve
to deal with their problems how they
should deal with them and then
what they present to the public
afterwards should be up to them not up
to
you know news reporters and you know tmz
level people following them around and
painting headlines and stories for us to
to fight about
yeah kanye like i've fallen off the
kanye train
just that i don't spend time like karen
but you brought the kim and that thing
or kim and kanye and early in the days
and this is before
i mean the internet really has taken
this weird twist that it has today
um but when you know kanye kind of like
went on stage
and you know blew up on taylor swift
like everybody saw that as like
like we hate kanye now like they're very
against him and
like i had no care like i don't love his
music but like i see him as a
person and he was going through so much
like you know his mom had died he was so
unbelievably close with his mom
like he was just going through so much
and
like no one ever stopped to go and like
hey is kanye
okay it just became like a clickbait
thing like let's go against kanye
like he's such a horrible person this is
like what he's done all these other
people
but like he was super edgy he just lost
his best friend
you know i saw what my mom went through
when she lost her mother and so like
on a personal level and a very small
like non-public way i can see like what
that does to a person but now when
you're always pushed in a limelight and
if you sneeze like
you know it's gonna end up in a tabloid
somewhere like
how that must destroy a person so he
wasn't able to heal
through a death of like a morning
because he was also having to deal with
like
all this publicity moments that he went
through and it's like how has that
turned him
into the person that you know he is
today that we saw on like
2019-2020 kanye you know
so he's a person i always like have a
heart for just because it's like
he was in a public eye and we i don't
think he ever got a chance to heal
i think that's kanye's issue and we're
still like digging at
kanye we haven't like let that go for
him in order to like
feel yeah and he even like the keeping
up with kardashians very show
a very popular show like they never he
never wanted to like be on the show
or like um he wasn't he would never
speak like
he might appear in the background but he
would never actually interview
or like talk to the cameras it's because
like he can't
move out of his house of a tv show
that's being filmed but he want to like
try and be out of limelight as much as
possible
yeah feel bad for him and it's so
happening
yeah oh it still is i mean there's a lot
of celebrities that are that go through
that too and it just doesn't
it doesn't make sense it's like we
shouldn't be feeding off of
that shouldn't be creating entertainment
like other people's loss or other
people's
you know moments like again like
we all get mad we all get upset
sometimes we get emotional
but like our friends or the people we're
interacting with often
like they they know us and they
understand and they're like you know
i get it and then you know an hour later
we're fine but
presenting it to the world we think it's
okay for us
as um you know
as as like like we're audience members
of someone's
life which is weird like this isn't
gladiator we're not sitting in here
in the coliseum watching two people like
yeah come on fight
like this is someone's life like what
what if what our new gladiator instead
of watching two men fight to the death
with swords
it's like a husband and wife and we're
like oh we want to know all of your
all of your drama like we want to oh she
said that oh the crowd
she tweeted like yeah yeah we're
watching it's like the public sphere has
gotten just
just really weird and out of control and
i think that like we're interacting with
it without
understanding what we're contributing to
it in a lot of ways i think um
i mean imagine like you were saying you
know you your grandmother you know
your mom you lost her mom imagine if she
had to go through that
this the day it happens she's got
cameras tmz
there's 50 people right outside the
hospital like they're like
so what you lost you you lost your mom
how do you feel you know
what what a maddening thing to do what a
maddening thing for anybody to go with
um again with kanye he chose to get up
on stage
you know there was a choice but but you
know he was going through
through some [__] so it's it's just kind
of like this
it is a big deal in a sense but there's
also i think with retrospect and time
you kind of almost see where he's coming
from you almost have that sympathy
of oh man that sucks like in he you know
he really took that moment away from
taylor swift and that that is sad in
itself you know she had to deal with
trauma now from that
but it doesn't mean that he is the
shittiest worst person in the world it
doesn't mean that he deserves to like
suffer it doesn't mean that
like all these mean things people say
about him like that's i don't know it's
it's uh it's it's hard to to run any
sort of life with cameras and
in social media and phones and stuff
pointed out your face yeah and i think
that's the root that i'm saying i'm not
saying that like
i mean definitely sexual assault's not
okay and like yeah
attacking people or hurting people
emotionally or physically is okay
it's the it's that we as like
to create entertainment we just like
digging at people more and more
we don't like let them be and then they
become prisoners into their own house
because that's the only place that's
safe that they can like have guards and
stuff
and it's like it's that that's not okay
and i think that's like
the worst that social media can do on
like a larger very public level
and then you know even in like high
school and stuff you have like cyber
bullying that's
a very real thing and then you just like
you
you kill at a human and like humanity
just because there's like a screen in
between
you and that person but you're still
saying these things that like
i wouldn't say in a large room that of a
crowd that i knew this person was
sitting in
it's just like that's just what's not
okay i mean it's that same thing i was
talking about with
posture and like the skills that you
learn from having those face-to-face
talks you
i mean like if i'm if i'm talking or
like
you know maybe i drink two cups of
coffee and i'm just going off and i'm
just cracking jokes and i'm like not
really aware of what i'm saying
but i noticed that i just kind of said
something like a joke that
took it too far and it just hurt this
person's feelings i'm gonna notice that
because i'm in person with them
and i'll be like oh okay you know i
didn't mean it like this i apologize or
whatever
i mean that's a strange example but
there's so much to be brought to the
table with
in person and um you know even just
visual and audio cues like have you used
um clubhouse at all the new app
oh i've heard about it you haven't
gotten on it yet
no i think trying of get off of social
media yeah i don't know
don't get it i think that it would pull
you in oh no
it's uh i haven't been too heavy on it
again like i've been trying to
you know have a social media break too
but that is one that i have kept on
um and it's there is something different
about vocal that there is something
different some of these conversations
like
some of these conversations are really
[__] good man like they're very
respectable
respectable people like i'm listening to
you know
evolutionary biologists and scientists
and um
like very very woke people discuss
what's going on um you know you're
listening to
people on the edge of like theories of
everything in physics
having discussions about their views and
what they've discovered
like they're um in you're you're
listening to
conversations that if it was just
written out or this was just papers or
it was just um
like i'm waiting for this person to
email me back to know what they think
about my theory of everything and blah
blah
like it's this you would never see these
people just
hey let's let's talk on the phone and
just kind of talk about this
whatever and we'll have in also on the
other line that can hear us
um is a thousand other scientists from
across the world
who can listen in on this conversation
so it's that there is something that
um there is head butting on clubhouse
there is
arguments on clubhouse but there's
something about having vocal tonality
where people start to talk over each
other they start to kind of like i don't
mean this or whatever
and then the moderator steps in and it
was like hey let's reset
let's let's bring it down and then they
continue the conversation
it's that does sound great yeah i think
that
yeah it's uh it's very interesting i've
been very fascinated i haven't said
anything i haven't um started my own
clubhouse rooms yet i've thought about
taking some like intense podcast
episodes like my sense making sickness
where we talk about you know cancel
culture and
these very like uh you know
fringe friend subjects that are
difficult to talk about that like even i
will
uh out loud maybe say the wrong things
but i don't want to be afraid to say the
wrong things
um i i'm thinking about perhaps
moving to clubhouse and it's kind of
like you can have
so two people on stage like if you're
the the moderator of of the room
you can make a room titled like cancel
culture
and then it's me and you know my friend
spencer and we're talking on the stage
but then
people start to join the room just
because you know they follow me or they
follow spencer
or they like the subject or whatever and
it starts growing
i can then invite people from the
audience to discuss with us
and be up on stage with us so
i think when it comes to problem solving
and again just the
the power of vocal tonality uh
i think it could be a a good dip out of
what social media has done to our
communication
you know because it almost sounds like
reddit but like with all the verbal and
social cues
yeah yeah i like that i like that i
think that's a good that's a good
comparison
yeah i have to check it out though i
don't like i'm trying to get rid of all
the social media like
i have to keep it because i work in
social media so like i have to keep my
facebook but i like delete the app and i
only go on
for work on my laptop and then but then
like snapchat is where my homies are and
then
instagram's like i feel like a healthier
facebook in a sense yeah
more conversational where like my close
friends were on instagram for me
facebook is a hard one man facebook
facebook to me
facebook is is like too far gone to me
it's vicious
it's and it's i i don't i don't mean
disrespect by this but i think
facebook being an older person thing and
um
less less understanding of how
technology truthfully works
there's a lot a lot of people on there
very
echo chamber very tribalistic behavior
on facebook
um it's uh yeah very opinionated
it's it's it's too far gone like like if
i just think
because i used to have when i had
facebook when i was like younger
started out this very casual just
posting kind of whatever and then
after a while i would start to be the
guy i'm like i'm good at seeing
holding two perspectives at once i'm
good at understanding where this
person's coming from and this person's
coming from
so i think and so i'm gonna be the guy
to save the day in the comments
i'm gonna be like i'm gonna try to give
the logical explanation this long drawn
out thing in the comments on someone's
like
nasty post like i used to spend a lot of
my like i would spend
35 minutes writing a reply to someone's
like nasty snarky facebook
because i'm like hey you just
misunderstand and i get what the other
side is saying
also i respect you and i don't want i
don't want them to see you in this wrong
light
it's but it's it's too far gone now man
there's not a lot of logic happening
there and there's all like click bait
articles on there which is like what was
so toxic for me
because i felt like all these news
channels and then like
world large events were happening i
would just get into it and get into like
the numbers of things and then
people like angry each other on social
media for like
their viewpoints it's like this is not
healthy like let me just
pull out of it like delete the app and
like
and i was checking on myself i'm like
this is this is what this app is making
me feel
but my hands just like go and click on
it and then that's like a time waster
for me
and so i was like nope i don't want to
lose these minutes of life and i also
like the amount of the feel inside it's
giving me is just not
worth it like there's no positiveness
out of it so
i have it for messenger because i talk
to my best friend
on facebook messenger and that's it and
then
um just for like work posts and stuff
but like even the few minutes i'll catch
myself like just sit and board at like
my
my console or something at work and i
have my laptop open and it's like oh
well i'm allowed to go to facebook now
and i click on it for a few minutes i
like i've been regretting it it's just
it's not if i want to like find out what
numbers are happening like i know google
them or i just like
sit on the news channels that i enjoy
and it's
it's it's been a much healthier social
media relationship so
i try and keep and track like if
instagram is going to start doing that
to me then i should start limiting my
time on that one more
and just like we need to get back to
just connecting with people
by like zoom calls or something yeah
not like what posts they decide to make
public that day to make an announcement
yeah you're totally right and i think
you have you know
just noticing like okay i'm scrolling on
this and then just having that noticing
a few minutes later of
this isn't the best thing for my time
right now or maybe this is making me
think about things
or um i'm now getting involved in in
social
you know you know discrepancies or
arguments that i actually really i just
don't have time for them right
right now i don't have time to put my
energy into this into this person's like
mellow drama
or um or or even if it's not drama even
if it's their life like
a lot of times when we're just trying to
casually like waste a couple minutes
it's enough to where we just got like
500 new things to think about over the
course of five minutes
where we should have just kind of kept
focus on our work
so we don't have to like bring our
attention back all the time you know and
so
yeah no but like you say that and then i
guess a mini replacement slash guilty
pleasure for me has been tick-tock
which is like all these like short
little things and you're like
really heavy thoughts and like a 15
second video
and you just like scroll for like 15
minutes and now you've seen
like probably 100 videos and that's a
lot of math
but and then i'm not sure would that be
no i'm bothered to be like well if each
one was 15 seconds
there's four times 15 that you've seen
like 60 videos
and i have like 60 new thoughts if
you're like super adhd
you know your brain is just full with
like all these different thoughts and
science and stuff and ah
that sounds like awesome and amazing but
not conducive to like
getting some [__] done i feel like it
should definitely be uh when i'm gonna
sit on tick tock should almost be
a like this is my designated free time
like i'm gonna let my mind go crazy i'm
gonna let like oh wow what a cool
thought
or you know oh wow just learned this
thing about this new dance move i'm
gonna try or i'm gonna
learn this thing about science i'm gonna
go look more into it but
it's it's not super helpful to have a
sudden like
like like to disrupt our day all the
time i mean
and i you know i i still deal with my
addictions when it comes to social media
for sure too you know i'm still
still working through them in my own
ways but um i i do notice
it pulls you away and it makes you think
about a million other things that you
weren't thinking about
and then trying to bring your attention
back to like dude i gotta get some work
done
i gotta edit this thing i've gotta show
up i've gotta talk to normal people
and i don't wanna just talk about
tick-tock videos to to to people in
person
so i've got to like be present what do i
need to be thinking about where do i
need to be
so yeah people that don't understand
tick tock you have to be
cause like i mean there's some judgment
on tech talk as well it's like oh i was
watching a video
that told me the science fact or like oh
i read this
article and it's like no it wasn't
either one of those it was a tick tock
video and then i got on like the tick
tock thread and then learned so much
more about that topic but like
you can't just say oh i watch a tick
tock on it like yeah they instantly
don't respect you
like okay so anything you're about to
say is not a real thing
right and they're like oh you're on tick
tock like no one fact-checks that but
it's like no it was like hank green he's
like a good scientist
and he was talking about cells and it
was so cool but like you can't say oh i
learned on tick tock
well and i think we have to look at our
attention spans in a real way
and look at you may have not ever even
learned or cared to learn about that
specific information if it wasn't you
know condensed into a nice bite-sized
enjoyable chunk if the only way you're
going to learn about this little corner
of science is from
somehow going to a lecturer or a college
course
to sit through it for a quarter then
that's a lot bigger deal than
being able to learn something really
cool the core of
like you know something that in even
those tick tock videos could spark your
interest
and make you want to go join the class
you know because it presents it in a way
that's simple and it's short and it's to
the point um i talk about um
i had him on instagram and he would
repost his tick tocks on there
um reed stefan who is a
music producer and he's he's like post
you know 25 seconds
how to make vocals sound good on a trap
track
and it'll just be 25 seconds of him
adding add this delay
and then you're gonna add this reverb
and then you're gonna do this to your
auto tune
and oh my gosh so much information in
one little clip
and i just learned so much from it it's
amazing like
you don't need all the fluff you just
need to know and then
like now you are going to try it maybe
learn a few other things
because you tried this one thing and
then now you're on like a creative
spree that you know maybe you weren't
originally gonna get sent on because you
didn't see that video
yeah that sounds fun but we gotta we
gotta
check ourselves so to some extent we
don't need to center yourself
like how long have i spent on tick tock
today oh i love that the like
swipe over feature on your oh i love it
and i hate it
but like you can see right especially
when it's like a non-work day
and then so like today i mean i've been
running around town i've been on my
phone for an
hour and three minutes and it'll like
show you like how much time you've
actually spent doing stuff like i've
been on 19 minutes just sitting on
messenger
probably texting people about work stuff
but like that's too much time
of my life and that's how much time has
like expelled like i'm not gonna get
back now
but yeah it's great and bad to know
yeah it's dude it's definitely changing
us it's definitely you know our
attention spans are
are changing and where i i really like
talking about
on the podcast i feel like uh i i have
some really good conversations like this
about social media and like our own
social media use because
we're kind of the age you know around
the age where
we got social media at like a young teen
age my space man
yeah yeah what do you remember how old
you were when you got myspace
it was definitely on a desktop i got it
because my youth group
all had it and we had like a feed
so i don't know i was young i'd have to
like think about it
yeah pretty young though yeah but i like
i didn't have a cell phone i definitely
had social media before i had a cell
phone i was 12 when i got a
cell phone so probably like 11 or 12 i
was on my space
i feel like that's right yeah yeah i
mean
well i guess maybe that's not so
different i mean i guess we didn't have
like nowadays you're having you know
very young kids like babies
go from like they already have an ipad
in their in their hand and stuff and
that enough is to change
i mean are the ages zero through nine
like this
is really you know changes a lot of who
we are and what we do and how we're
gonna be for the rest of our life
and so yeah i mean we're we're
i i i enjoy just kind of speaking on the
differences because
because so much of this stuff we just do
without thinking about it we're just
we're just doing it's like the new
iphone came out so i got it and then
it's like wait
why do why do i have the iphone like
what does it do for me
what is it doing to me if i didn't have
it what would i be like
if i you know there's all these things
that where
we're kind of just living the life
that's given to us on
on the platter in a lot of ways but i
think that our age group
can really be helpful in the future to
young kids
you know like we're talking about um you
know just having social interaction
these kids are going to grow up and not
be able to have a lot of face-to-face
conversations
and that that could be harmful to to to
their
you know to their feelings about
themselves um you know but like
you and i also oh sorry i cut you off
like you and i also were handed like
i don't want to say like a seven-course
appetizer but like
we had to transition into social media
so like now
you've got me thinking about my timeline
like you know 11 or 12 i had a myspace
before i had a cell phone
at 12 i got a cell phone i could only do
calls and i had a facebook before i had
a phone
that could even like search on the
internet or anything like that
so whereas like now kids are having like
cell phones or also an internet machine
and they're like here
and then they can go and get you know
snapchat
clubhouse reddit facebook instagram like
all of them all at once whereas like we
sort of more or less i guess faded out
of in-person conversations so we still
craved that because we know
the benefits of them whereas like you
and like
kids today are just like this is how you
communicate go sore
and that's like that's really
interesting never thought about that
before
that speed yeah yeah i know yeah heck
yeah
uh i mean where we're
learning like what we're noticing as we
go to we're like
okay like this doesn't feel super good
because we're used to
actually also having the in-person
conversation so maybe we're actually in
a even more important
position of noticing the contrast um
you know being older like we still
understand technology it's not like
because you know you go 10 years above
us and a lot of people
technology is like just a very difficult
thing for them to they're still like
learning how to not peck when they type
on the keyboard
you know so yeah you know i i
which i just foresee a lot of
strange um social
and like biochemical bio
we're going to deal the young kids are
going to grow up
and deal with new things that humans
have never dealt with before
and i don't know if that's going to come
out psychologically if it's going to be
like
physical to if it's going to be um you
know
we like what we have been for thousands
of years
suddenly changed in 14 years iphone came
out 2007
you know and we're going to have it's
not going to be like
kids are going to start [__] melting
and then they can't have real person
conversations or anything you know
but there is going to be some mental
health related issues
that young people are going to have to
navigate and deal with
you know on their own and i hope that
our age group is able to
you know offer them some helpful advice
you know yeah but
isn't our generation the most anxious
generation
yeah i think so i think i've seen that
somewhere which i believe oh yeah
i feel that i mean it's probably a lot
from social media like where suddenly
all of our social structures
are put in front of our face and now we
have to worry about them in ways that we
never really thought about before we
were just
interacting and doing our thing before
and now we know it exists
we know where we should fit in it and we
know how to present ourselves
to fit in it you know oh my gosh
facebook even has like a feature and
i've seen it
where it's like the timeline features so
you can like
like megan robinson bought a house and
it's literally like an option
it's like pre-built into facebook like
you know megan robinson is engaged to
blank or like
whatever you want and it's like a whole
timeline in our life like it's pure
pre-curated but it's just not it's not
built that way it's crazy i mean our
whole life
our whole life is an interview in a way
right like oh my gosh
you're now living through a lifelong
interview
like what have you done what have you
accomplished and like there's a point
where you know an employer who's
who's probably you know like like higher
if you're applying for a job at
uh you know apple or tesla like they
probably have some pretty good
people who are searching like your
background before they hire you
you know or if you're hired as someone
who's gonna have like an opinion or
like represent a company they're going
to scrub your whole history
they're going to look at you know not
your history but like what you've posted
who you are who what you've been tagged
in like you know have a lifelong of
of interviewing yeah that's supposed to
represent who you are which is the wrong
way to look at humans but it's something
we're going to deal with
i have friends that like care so much
about what their
portfolio looks like and like what do
what do their financial portfolios look
like like how much do they have in
stocks like do they own a house yet
like they almost carry and it's not like
social media they
stray up just care like what does my
portfolio look like and that's all
they'll talk about
is like what stocks they have or like
how much they're worth
and it's like that's like that's not
what matters when you're
at the end when your meat pod goes bad
and you need to
you know go on to whatever is next it's
like that stuff doesn't carry over into
the next
the next game the next video whatever
you want to call it
yeah like like what does that stuff have
to do with with
love and beauty in in
relationships and family and friendships
you know and
like those are it's almost like our our
our society overlay sometimes takes hold
of us
and takes us away from like the realness
of what we are
as as you know humans with with brains
and
emotions and and all this and all these
intricate things
lately have been like you know the
panoramic has made me
a lot more appreciative of like the
moments so like
when we were all locked in our houses i
would like look at photos and like the
things that we've done or like our
travel opportunities that we've
both had and like enjoying those moments
so like lately since like things are
coming back out and people are leaving
our homes and i'm gonna go places again
i'm like getting angry at myself because
the past few months i've always been
like looking down at my screen like
trying to like see what the outside
world looks like
and then i have to like catch myself and
it's it's really hard i want to do
better at but i like want to look up
more
and like look at the world and like live
in the moment and try and figure out how
to like
live in the present and not worry about
like the next five things that i need to
go do
um and like enjoy all these like little
moments we have because like we all lost
it in like a day
um but like those are the things that
like
carry over and like continue not like
our financial portfolios or like what
our credit score is
so important apparently in order to
exist in our
economic world but like those aren't
the top things that like everybody
should be walking around
having to like brag about yeah yeah i
mean they're
it's it's not that they're not important
you know they for sure are
but they shouldn't be the the starting
point of how you meet everybody or like
the starting point of how you represent
yourself or everything you think about
you know it's
it's a i've said this before is either
timothy leary or rom das had repeated it
um always was it always keep in mind
your
buddha nature and your social security
number
and it's it's it's that's how it is i
mean you've got to notice on on both but
i think that
you know recognizing i'm a human with
emotions and like that's what's
important in
in my relationships with people like
actual relationships are important
and the rest of the stuff is just that's
plus you know and that the rest of the
stuff sometimes gets you gets you to
your right relationships but
for the most part like what's the core
of why you're getting those things like
once you get money
it's you want to have all this money or
you want to have all this comfort or
this
safety so you can feel what like
wholeness with your being you can feel
at ease you can feel peace you know
you're you're trying to get these things
to obtain
some sort of emotion or uh mode of being
that that meets makes you most
comfortable so um
we've done we've definitely had a lot of
uh
great trips like i was as you were
talking about about our trips i was
immediately thinking of uh
i think it was was it san francisco
or san diego we went to anaheim
and i well and then what south what
south of anaheim it was like an hour
away 45 minutes away where we went to
that
that was a cool beach that wasn't malibu
no i tagged it because it was like that
was the photo that i went through and i
was like
we need to repost this it was the pier
and then it got cold and we got cool
jackets
yeah we went to this uh gas station yeah
that's what dude
our team has had such a good time
together our you know we're we're
co-workers but
we all seem to like aren't we went to
connection beach
huntington beach yeah oh cool wait yeah
hold that up again oh gosh
yeah i started talking so the camera
switched to me i wanted to make sure
everybody saw it that's that's a
wonderful photo
that was that you had a man bun like
then
i had a man bone i miss it i'm gonna
grow my hair back out i'm gonna grow the
whole thing back out this time but
what good memes though yeah i mean we
yeah
we have a lot of good times i mean
you've done a lot a lot of traveling
you've been traveling when did you start
traveling for work like how old were you
15 yeah yeah i worked on a tv show
and i went to um i was based off florida
i went to pennsylvania i was in
pittsburgh so i was like okay i can get
free housing like take me there and then
um they took me out to las vegas to
finish the season finale
it was pretty cool you remember what you
what were you doing like what was your
show role
oh i was like a production assistant for
nbc show
nice yeah it was a mega ninja warrior
but i just don't like
running around with that yeah it was
really cool you're not trying to name
drop that is super cool though
i don't want to be known for that for
like a year or two i was like oh she
works on american and jewelry i don't
want
i don't want that i get that though i
mean you're super multifaceted though
you
like you you do a lot of things you know
your way around uh camera and video
camera
very well too i just like to help people
do whatever i can
yeah you're very helpful i mean you are
aware
of of like feelings and situations that
other people
aren't like i remember like there was a
time in pennsylvan i think it was
pennsylvania where everyone got sick
and then like we're all sitting there
just suffering and blowing in our
napkins and you like set down like
vitamins and
and like you're like oh i went and took
care of this and i also got batteries
and i got this
like you're just aware that was when i
was a
i was a drug dealer for all of you we
laughed about because every four hours i
was like guys it's time to take our
medicine
yep time to take your medicine team
oh we were all dying i was like um
on snapchat there's like a feature where
you can like see your previous snaps
and so um i was like pennsylvania had
popped up and it was like we're all
dying and i like look
sick and like i had a video of like one
of their my interns bringing me a capri
sun
and then we were just yeah that was a
time
we have had good shows you haven't been
able to like travel as much since you're
like
since it's virtual and you can like send
us your files yeah but
every show you're so mentioned it's like
oh we have the jake file we're good
cool yeah that's all that's always super
sweet to hear i know like
i feel like you guys will message me or
abriel will message me like ah
this music is just making it or she'll
like you know um you know
the boss will say something and she'll
text me like oh he's really appreciating
this or or whatever it makes me feel
uh like i'm i'm kind of there with y'all
yeah
no you definitely are like um there was
this one song
and i couldn't say what song is now i'd
have to ask tyler but
he like we were all concerned that it
was gonna be all the profanity was about
to hit
and then you just like changed the song
right before
like the profanity should have hit and
it like transitioned so well
and it's just like oh jake jake just
knows how to how to make it clean for
all the years
it was really cool moment yeah i've got
a couple years of uh
listening for cuss words experience
underneath my belt at this point
and now it's like something uh i did i
did a wedding on saturday
and man like even playing
my tags that are marked clean i'm i'm
going to play them and i'm listening
through it really quickly in my
headphones and i'm like i can't play
that
it's clean because it edits it out but
it's literally talking about very vulgar
stuff
or it'll say you know like like even a
song saying sex
the word sex or sexy too much is very
uncomfortable to play to children
you know yeah and so there's even yeah
and so i'm like looking for all these
little things it's not just like oh it's
the dirty version or the clean version
or it's the bleeped version or the not
i mean there's like so many i have to
assess what the lyrics mean what they're
hinting at
and make sure it's just not something
that's too right below the surface where
everybody's like i know what that means
you were saying that vulgar thing with a
little bit different a word
it's a it's hard yeah i remember there
was this one show where i picked a uh
a song for a video that i need to edit
which was like an overview of our
conference
and you um had caught that that might
not have been
a good song choice and then boss man was
sitting there
and then like the three of us are just
sitting there and you instantly like
pulled up the lyrics i remember
boss man seen it as like a really
impressive moment
because like you don't just like listen
to it and go like oh yeah that's fine
like no you actually read it to like
make sure that there's not like a little
like undercut
lyric that's in there that might be
misinterpreted oh yeah it's so
nerve-wracking to like if i hear
if i hear something my butt is just so
puckered i'm just like oh man
like like if if i think it's coming i'll
even like as i'm listening to it play
out if i've already checked it
and it's the clean version but i know
the regular version normally says
something else
as it's playing over the speakers i'm
still kind of like
i know that i checked that one but like
did i put the wrong file
is it about to say [__] really loud or
i don't know but that's like like the
kids aren't being
filtered that either like it's only like
shows and
schools and concerts that like have to
do it but like
again the kids can just like go and
click on whatever they want and so get
exposed to that like i remember
back in the day when like we bought like
albums right like cds that hard case cds
you know a paper in them
um and like there used to be a sticker i
guess it's still on there
now but like yeah parental advisory like
explicit like that was a question mark
if like i could get that album at like
hot topic or something it's like well
who
is this and like if it was a certain
artist it was like oh okay look we like
them they're fine
but then like others it's like oh no
this is an explicit album like we can't
get that right yeah no i don't think
that's a thing
i i i i can't imagine it is i mean
because spotify's explicit tag is
very crappy it's so crappy right there's
like
yeah there's popular songs that that
are like the today's top hits like
number one everybody listens to this
exact one
and there's no explicit tag next to it
but like in the chorus it's saying [__]
you know like how do you filter that out
like does the parent like log on to
spotify or apple music and then
like type in a password and like no we
don't want our child having this
unclean music and then they just don't
have access to all of spotify
but then they're there but then
spotify's tags would have to be more
accurate than they are
and you would have to have some sort of
like designated
these are bad words these references are
bad that we don't want our kids to hear
tyler and i talked about this on a
podcast in i mean i i
i think it's so much simpler than it is
but then you start discussing it and
it's like oh man this is a very
complicated issue like
what's a cuss word why is a cuss word
bad uh
like should we be completely not letting
kids listen to it should we be leaving
up to their parents to explain to them
hey like it's okay for you to hear this
but i would like for you to not repeat
this because it's a bad word because
this
or you know whatever i think that's up
to parents as individuals i don't know
that there should be
one big clean words police but uh it is
interesting
we still are holding on to this parental
advisory explicit tag
but it's not working it's like where
it's just this old thing
that's broken but we're not addressing
it we're just kind of like
yeah let's let's do we're doing the
thing hey we put explicit on it because
it said the cuts were like we did our
our work but they're not all the time so
it's crazy i know youtube
they have like a generator where like
even if certain words are used
you have to like use you have to be like
signed in and like it verifies that
you're 13 years or older like 18 plus
but like even that's not good if you can
just like switch your parents account on
like on your youtube web page because
you have a shared computer or something
yeah
because like their parents don't know
how to do that sort of thing but kids
are like oh i know exactly how to do
this
like oh i know my parents password i'll
just change it and watch this video and
it's fine
their password is my name with a one
after it
oh no the dead giveaway um
well we are getting kind of up here in
time megan
um i've really appreciated this
conversation what what do you have
what do you have coming up like what's
so you've been working your butt off the
last
60 days you've been moving around you
were saying i think so
yeah so what what have you been doing
lately like you've been doing
is it a lot more video work are you
doing production assistant stuff
a little of everything i've been um
traveling around doing
like coved shows is what we call them so
we we still build a stage
as if like an audience would be there
but then just the people that are on
stage
are present and then like the immediate
workers and then we don't have an
audience and then we just like live
stream out
so i've been hopping around cydia city
doing that and then in between that
i have been um doing drive-in shows
so florida's pretty open right now with
the panoramic
and but like they're so hesitant about
doing like indoor stuff or like super
crowded stuff
so um another company i work for we have
these stages that are trailers and they
just like open up
and then um then we like put all of our
production stuff
on it and build led walls that way
people can see and then
we'll have concerts so we have like ali
and aj and a few other
like rappers and comedians recently come
on stage so
whenever i'm not traveling i've been
home working on those shows and
easter we have drive-in church where
everybody like pulls up to our stages
and churches happening on stage safely
and then they tune into their radio
station and they can see on our giant
like led walls
like church that's happening so i'll be
like live switching for that this easter
i think that's going to be something
nice i think that's going to be cool
actually
it's great i've done them before this
will be my fourth drive-in church
session and it's the same church that we
have and it's just really cool like
they're very loud
church and it's a great session yeah
that's what i have what about yourself
what do you have coming up
oh man my life is is weird right now
um i as far as live events i don't
really have
have much of anything um i've done like
a couple of virtual things
like for forest ibis and whatnot but um
because i'm
i'm moving actually did i tell you i'm
moving you did you're moving to texas
you're gonna be a texan
i'm gonna be a texan yeah and so um yeah
spoiler anybody
who is a listener of the podcast that's
the first mention of that i am moving
out to texas
um so so i i'm at this point where
um i don't really know what's next for
me i don't really know
like what's coming up i don't really
know even what my career choice is fully
going to be right now
um because i'm really i'm really trying
to take this as
it is a big deal i've lived in this town
my whole life and so my first move you
know my move away i i
i'm recognizing how you know this really
could be a great
beautiful wonderful transitional moment
to me
in my future and what i want to do and
you know you know i've got a lot of
ideas and
and um you know some plans but nothing
super solid right now
so um i'm just gonna go try to really
really be present
and you know and just just really be
there and be
um you know open to opportunities
open to you know like dare i say it open
to synchronicities
open to listening to my intuition you
know i'm really i really have this like
strong um
inner in inner uh faith if i want to you
know
overuse the the spiritual words um
but that that it's what i'm supposed to
be doing like i'm very pulled to this
place for for whatever reason at this
time in my life
and so i'm kind of just hoping that it
that it unravels as it should
when i get there so yes if you want it
it will
unravel even if like that's how i
believe that that's how it works even in
like my hardest times like it
has worked out even if it doesn't feel
like it does like at the end i'm like oh
it worked out
so i know for you since you want it and
you are who you are like
it's going to be great whatever it is
wherever you want to go thank you megan
i appreciate that
i appreciate that i'm i'm looking
forward to it i'm looking forward to
to the journey you know i mean we'll see
what happens
yeah what what do you have do you have
anything going on in in your
personal project life like of course are
you doing um
because i think you have a photography
page on instagram don't you are you
i do on that lately it's very dead um
i haven't had time to post it and that's
sort of its own entity
but yeah i do videography and
photography on the side
i do like engagement shoots and lately
i've been doing a lot of like post
processing on lightroom but
i'm really good at sharing my photos
with all the people
that i take them off but i'm really bad
at sharing them to the pages that
i should be sharing them to so i just
like people to have their photos and
enjoy them
yeah nothing wrong with that um so is
is there any any product or anything
that you want to have people keep an eye
on like any
anything you want to nah now we're good
good you're just working
i can yeah just keep chugging
okay thanks for the opportunity of a
shout out yeah
yeah of course i just want to make i
mean i think you're a cool person i
think you're really good at what you do
like all the things that you're
that you're like your mind is just very
good in a live event setting
like you just have so many different
things covered and it's like if megan's
on it
it's good it's good i appreciate you
trust it i appreciate that
i love working with you and i miss
working with you too my friend asked why
maybe maybe uh the large national show
yeah yeah i've got a i i do have a
couple emails i need to respond to
um in terms of that but um we will see
it's
hard to plan it all out but but but
we'll see we'll hopefully see you in
person soon
yes i hope so um megan it's been
wonderful i
thank you for for uh making this happen
i know that we had like rescheduled it a
couple times and
we're just busy people man yeah yeah
so uh i wish you the best of luck in
your busy endeavors
going forward um let's let's uh catch up
in the next couple weeks
um i'll definitely once this is ready to
release and whatnot i'll uh
shoot you another text sounds good yeah
we'll be in touch all right megan have a
good rest today listeners take care of
yourselves
drink some water do a little stretching
uh
you know look at the back of your
ingredients what are you putting into
your body
how much social media are you using is
social media using you
are you arguing with other people are
you identifying with things that aren't
really you
are you really getting the most out of
your human experience
right here because you're love and
that's what you should focus on
love love yourself peace out have a good
rest of your day bye megan thank you
again
at what age do we learn how to have
better conversations
at what age do we learn to have better
conversations with ourselves
[Music]
knowledge is power
reality is